My number one tip to becoming the best host is to use this cocktail mix that only uses natural ingredients that anyone can drink because they are vegan, gluten friendly, and only 25 calories.
One of my resolutions this year was to be more conscious about what I was putting into my body.
And I was shocked when I discovered how many artificial ingredients and preservatives the cocktail mixers that I was using had in them.
Not only was it bad for my health, but it also just didn't taste good now that I think about it.
I wanted to see if there were healthier alternatives, so I asked my bartender friend if he had any recommendations.
And he told me about these mixers that he's been using at home when he doesn't feel like going the whole nine yards for one cocktail.
He chose them specifically because of how good they tasted, but also because they use all natural ingredients.
I gave them a try for a party I hosted over the weekend and everybody was telling me how yummy they were and we're asking for the recipes.
So I told them that it was the super easy to use instant cocktail mixers by this company called Craft Mix.
It has the cutest packaging, but the best part is that they're super transparent about their ingredients list so you don't have to worry about artificial ingredients or preservatives in your drink.
They're also gluten free, vegan, and only 25 calories each.
I love carrying them around when I'm traveling because I can just whip up my favorite cocktail within minutes without going grocery shopping,
cutting up the ingredients, and making a mess.
So if you want to upgrade your cocktail game while still being health conscious, go and try Craft Mix's variety pack.
I promise you won't be disappointed.